{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Astra', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V11', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D27', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall Rio X', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution - 5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8A', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Conquest S12', 'manufacturer': 'Celkon', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Zeon 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93 India', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M30', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 5 MP (ultrawide) + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo), upgradable to Android 9.0 (Pie) + One UI'}
{'device_name': 'vivo Y91i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + Funtouch 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M10', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo EF8 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V9', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Yandex Smartphone', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5302G Velvet 2', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Santin Max 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xolo Era 4X', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V2', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MiGuer M1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V5X', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V3', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 9', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'iLA X1', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Santin N1 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V3', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze Y3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody M78 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor, Face Unlock'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with Emotion 9.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V4', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y6 Prime 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Santin N1', 'manufacturer': 'Sonim', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E13', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D28', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.02 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee Y7', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Nubia Red Magic Mars', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with CMOS Sensor, f2.0 Aperture, 1080p Video'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie with Nubia Red Magic 1.6 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo NEX 2', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AL140', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 5C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Fly View Max', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E11', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BL250', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 4 High version', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Aqua', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 5', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor V20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA X2', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI F1', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Elegance E7', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP T155', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 4 Standard version', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.1 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A509 Jeans', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Wize YA3', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Play', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Power P11', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X60', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Plum Phantom 2', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Power P8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-40', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X80', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S10 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda K30', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A7', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 8', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GL355', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Max 1', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony E90', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-4', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis N1-550 Cruiser', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C1 Shine', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda K10', 'manufacturer': 'Kult', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS80', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy M20', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/1.9, 1/3.1", 1.12µm, PDAF + 5 MP, f/2.2, 12mm (ultrawide)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP, f/2.0, 25mm (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo), upgradable to Android 9.0 (Pie); One UI'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G355', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C2', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme U1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-3', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP402', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome Fenmmy Note', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B245', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI S3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '48MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Stock Android 9 Pie + Luxury Ceramic Design'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C1', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-2', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel S10', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Ukozi Uone', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A3', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A511 Harmony', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Infinity 12', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Top', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar C1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze H5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Play', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad M3', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A3', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Z455', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y7 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia M3', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Infinity 11', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ginzzu RS8502', 'manufacturer': 'Great Wall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tambo TA-1', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'itel P13 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y Max', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + EMUI 8.2'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XL4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U25 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Jet', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'itel A15', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Luck NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier I8', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Benefit M9', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Ace', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'itel A14', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B450', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5 Pro GT', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Z250', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo X5', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ark Wizard 2', 'manufacturer': 'Ark Elf', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar E1 Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5 Pro GT', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5s', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu V7', 'manufacturer': 'Plum', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS 4.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze U3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MiGuer M1', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom R17', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP B255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo AX7 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A512 Harmony Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'No'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Wigor V5', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Goophone Note 9', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1X Evolve', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Voto V12', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BL150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Vira', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5015L First', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Desire 12s', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Uniwa F4000', 'manufacturer': 'Uhans', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vargo VX3', 'manufacturer': 'Voyo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Sunset NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor X2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6T McLaren Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen 9.0 (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody S9', 'manufacturer': 'Xtouch', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cricket Wireless Wave', 'manufacturer': 'CMCC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Core 55S Ultra', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG X5 Android One', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.26 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Cricket Wireless Vision', 'manufacturer': 'CMCC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Aero', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V94', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Flash', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Haier Alpha A6', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 7S', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E500S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav M5', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Spark Go', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z81', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X21s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze V3 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Pixel 4', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Pluto', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Toughbook P-01K', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade Max 2s', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS60Z', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Energy E500', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y95', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y5 Lite 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (Go edition) + EMUI 8'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Illumina', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI One Max', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS40G', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Symbol Max', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS50G', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'iLA R1', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P85 NXT', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'GuoPhone X3', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A5 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Symbol S8L', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y73', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS50X', 'manufacturer': 'M-Horse', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark Helo 256GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 10MP + 8MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot A5', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Symbol S9L', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A5', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C10', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '3.15 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X23 Symphony Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P60', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Rosso', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 3', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5710 Infinity X1', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP (wide), AF + 5 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP (wide)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Haier P10', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera DuraForce Pro 2', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9600 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Stock Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos R2 Compact', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.57 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon 11', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic 2 256GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R17 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q9', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone U2', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu Note 8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze G5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A23', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i5014 Evo M4', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 6', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max Pro (M2)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'RED Hydrogen One', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Aura', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nomi i4500 Beat M1', 'manufacturer': 'Nomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max (M2)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y73 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot Quest', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart 2019', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Z1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Red Magic 2 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Y27', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Mix 3 512GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Red Magic 2', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T8', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Y28', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo S10', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel IdeaXTRA', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5s', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu C9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav Symbol X', 'manufacturer': 'Haier', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo S5 Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Feel 2', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C8', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y91', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + Funtouch 4.5'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Z9', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu C9', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M8 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'VOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 106 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Zeon 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Slimline', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y93', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'AGM A9', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda T55', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Hot 6X', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis N1-570 Space', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H12 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Bravis A510 Jeans', 'manufacturer': 'Bravis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5i', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung W2019', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel PowerPro P41', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5X Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U9', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V155', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U9 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 3.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertu Aster P Baroque', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Inoi 5X', 'manufacturer': 'Inoi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Advance 5.2 HD', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'T-Mobile REVVL 2', 'manufacturer': 'TCL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Black Shark Helo', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda T50', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP A150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HTC Exodus 1', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn K9 Smart Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi MIX 3 Palace Museum Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 MP + 2 MP with Aperture F2.0, Popp-up Front Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo) MIUI (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertu Aster P Gothic', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel LX', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview A10 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Mann 8S 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Max (M1) ZB556KL', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Polaroid Cosmo C6', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 5 Infinity Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Lite (L1)', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Allview A10 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5002G Fun', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Advance A6 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Polaroid Cosmo K2', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Xpression Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Оreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Infie 77', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5520L Silk', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense King Kong 4 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Bharat 4 Diwali Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo Go', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y81i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1 Plus 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda Y20', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense King Kong 4', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Magic 2', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS650', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda W55', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy Max 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iLA 7P', 'manufacturer': 'iLA', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS550', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Grand M2 2018 16GB', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone PX', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Photo Pro', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6s 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J4 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X11', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X7 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart X9', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X10S', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U23', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hotwav M5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart E9', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5 Style', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4608 x 3456 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade View Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z1 Youth Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Joy 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S80 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga X1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8C 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3 V1813BA', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 44', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga X1', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6016L Mercury', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ54', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone 5 Selfie Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 RS Porsche Design', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense 2', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Innelo 1', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'EL K20', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X7', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG it V36', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 X', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X26', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V145', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 (2019)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + EMUI 8.2'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ53', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Zero', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.6 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '9.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D26', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Ukozi U5', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Indigo', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V98', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP A140', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Y25', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S209', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Compact 4G', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8C', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Highscreen Power Five Max 2', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Y24', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 11', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 530', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Crosscall Trekker-X4', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5517L Twin Pro', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 5 Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K7 Power', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad E2C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense A6', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A7 Vita', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Crosscall Core-X3', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.1 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mann 8S', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/2.0 + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, Portrait Mode'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP571', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi iPro', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Razer Phone 2', 'manufacturer': 'Razer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Crosscall Action-X3', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 7.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Tommy 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Palm Phone', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade X2 Max', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C11', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meiigoo S9', 'manufacturer': 'Meiigoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Platinum P9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee M3', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 22', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu X8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy Max', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel Tetra', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart C9', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP1', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C1', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K1 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Platinum P9 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo K1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8x', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with Single-LED and AF Dual Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Symbol X', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Screen Fingerprint Edition 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom S17', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 11', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3T', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with, Face Recognition, f/2.2 Aperture, Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Orbit', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx X1 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Advance L4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Screen Fingerprint Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M11', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Alfa 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu V8 Standard version', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Power 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition, 3P lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Pay 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7S', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme C1', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu V8', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Rebel 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7 3GB', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6200L Aurora', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot King Kong 3', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Ray 600', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5300G Velvet View', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Vox V40 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7 Deluxe', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze F5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Y9 (2019) 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 2 MP depth sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo) + EMUI 8.2'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P10 Style', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon iAir2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Base 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S7', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 9 Plus 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z3i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Lite 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.9, 1.4μm + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S80', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sigma Mobile X-treme PQ37', 'manufacturer': 'Sigma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA3', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.87 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels f/1.9, 1.4μm + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 8GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 10MP + 8MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Experience 9.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i2x', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A6s', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'AGM H1', 'manufacturer': 'AGM', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI A3', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'nubia Z18s', 'manufacturer': 'Nubia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with 80 Degree Wide Angle Lens, F2,0 Aperture, 1.12 um pixel size, Face recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Nubia UI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '24MP + 10MP + 8MP + 5 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Experience 9.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5710', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Interpolated Resolution 13MP, Secondary front camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP (wide), AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 6', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nomu S50 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 6 Pro 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio Mega 2018', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11 SD660', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H12', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Note 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Konka D9', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Pass Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star Pro 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4501G Fox Easy', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A7', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone Xs Max', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.16 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max SD660', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5000G Velvet Easy', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cat S48c', 'manufacturer': 'CAT', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Z355', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Click2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 4.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone Xs', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.16 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo M10', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Grand M2 2018', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Apple iPhone Xr', 'manufacturer': 'Apple', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (f/2.2, 29mm, 1/3", 1.22 µm), phase detection autofocus'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.2 MP (f/2.4, 31mm), 720p@30fps, face detection, HDR, FaceTime over Wi-Fi or Cellular'}, 'operating_system': 'iOS 12'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9600 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with f/2.2 Aperture, Wide-Angle Lens - 80.4 degree'}, 'operating_system': 'Stock Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze E5 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 3', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels f/1.8'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with, Face Recognition, f/2.2 Aperture, Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx X1 Pro 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Power 5S', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP + 5MP with Interpolated to 13MP, Face Recognition, F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Doov V31', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Archos Access 57', 'manufacturer': 'Archos', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Zen Admire Blaze', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': '360 N7 Pro', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16X', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos D10', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji Z33', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade A4', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus V4', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Grace P7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y55', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R17', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': '360 N7 Lite', 'manufacturer': '360', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': '360 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi PocoPhone F1 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X6', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS80', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'ioutdoor X', 'manufacturer': 'ioutdoor', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J2 Core', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y50', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi PocoPhone F1', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS55M', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max SD636 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7C AUM-L41', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with Emotions 8.0 UI'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y10', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo T8s', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Power Max P490', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo X23', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max SD636', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'E&L Y30', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Axon 9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Mega 5A', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS50L 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Smartisan Nut Pro 2S', 'manufacturer': 'Smartisan', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels (f/1.8 Aperture) + 5 Megapixels (f/2.0 Aperture)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Smartisan 6.6.5'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei 8x', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom C2', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 4 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with LG UX'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F9 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.5 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS60F', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Candy', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Yota Devices YotaPhone 3', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 Note 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo AX5', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F9', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Multilaser MS60F Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Power Plus 3', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG V40 ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D24', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'YU Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Yu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Live (L1) Go Edition', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z60s', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 4.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'HTC U12 Life', 'manufacturer': 'HTC', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo S6 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS100', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Andy 4E5 8GB', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z91E', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Star OS 4.2 (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Epic T', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel U17', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion XL150 Abakan', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix S3X', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'X OS Hummingbird 3.3 Lite (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B4', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Konka D8', 'manufacturer': 'Konka', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B5Fox Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'itel A45', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V9 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz Andy 5E5', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao E-Sport', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Black Fox B5', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 7C 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'itel A22 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P8', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Key2 LE 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo H7s', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress City', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel C12 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE V9', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A22', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GM3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Key2 LE', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 7C', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'NUU Mobile G2', 'manufacturer': 'NUU Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y83 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Yota Devices Yota 3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Yotaphone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7 Plus ThinQ', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'itel A62', 'manufacturer': 'itel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Eluga Y', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Atom 3G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C5', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Allview P4 Quad', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y97', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P10', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XI Plus', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S55 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': '10.or D2', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A7x', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP AS160', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel M5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7 Fit', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9 with 80 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with LG UX'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel WP2', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'UMIDIGI Z2 Special Edition', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16.37 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Realme 2', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q8 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG G7 One', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9 with 80 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Maimang 7', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V11', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R15 Neo', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Yezz 4E7', 'manufacturer': 'Yezz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Visual UI (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Bluboo D6', 'manufacturer': 'Bluboo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Aquaris C', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Google Pixel 3', 'manufacturer': 'Google', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Mate 20 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze E7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee BL5500 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Aperture F2.2'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GH7i', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y81s', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus E3', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X3', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Click NFC', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo F8s', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i120', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4608 x 3456 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Forest', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X1i', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ginzzu RS9602', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus Z20', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i15', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5516L Twin', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji Z11', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Leagoo Power 2', 'manufacturer': 'Leagoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Leagoo OS 3.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo R17 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.2 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Vivo XI', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 9.0 Pie'}
{'device_name': 'Vestel Venus Go', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone T2', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony G100', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko View 2 Go', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Harry 2', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Lions 6', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Funk', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'JVC J20', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 8X Max', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OnePlus 6T', 'manufacturer': 'Oneplus', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.84 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Oxygen (Android 9.0 Pie)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 7', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola P30 Play', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Sky 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.4 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.6 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Ace', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.4 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Reef', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'E&L K20', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, 1.127 um pixel size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A30', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp C10', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9N 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp B10', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda V5', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Optim', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S506m', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Zopo Flash X2i', 'manufacturer': 'Zopo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S1', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with Interpolated resolution - 5 MP, F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XA2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22.87 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV6800 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9N', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Hercls A15', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A3s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'HiSense H18', 'manufacturer': 'Hisense', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 10 256GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z61 2GB', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG Harmony 2', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5056 Fresh', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Hercls L925', 'manufacturer': 'Hasee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Grand Prime Plus 2018 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao Imagine 5 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U7 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Vega', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Coolpad Cool Play 7', 'manufacturer': 'Coolpad', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android OS with CoolUI'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U7', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S70 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Land Rover Explore', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X70', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z61', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Grand Prime Plus 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Nova 3', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.2 + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (EMUI 8.2) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee K10 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Recognition. ArcSoft'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note9 Exynos', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone Armor 5', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo V9 6GB', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit A150', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Note9 SD845', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 5V', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel K8', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Toughbook FZ-N1', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 10 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia X5', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'AllCall S1', 'manufacturer': 'AllCall', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 MP + 2 MP Megapixels with 1.2 um Pixel Size, Interpolated Resolution 5MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'THL T9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'THL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with SW 8.0MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z1i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Highscreen Expanse', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI One', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture, Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone P11', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 5', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Note 10 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Win', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.81 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K11 Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V135', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'UMiDIGI One Pro', 'manufacturer': 'UMiDigi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition, 5P Lens, F2.0 Aperture, Samsung S5K3P3 ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Blade', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee K10', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with Face Recognition. ArcSoft'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone A2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar S20', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylo Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG K11 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Sol 3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao Note5x', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Elephone Soldier', 'manufacturer': 'Elephone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21 Megapixel Sony IMX220'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes 16 Megapixel with Aperture f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Eclipse', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Play Android Oreo (Go Edition)', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y15 64GB', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi A2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, OmniVision OV5675 PureCel Sensor, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 NougatAndroid 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Sugar Y15 32GB', 'manufacturer': 'Sugar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto Z3', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Indie 15', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao R15', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 1', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z10', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, 5P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 3.2 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Pocket 18×9', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zen Admire Infinity', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'LG X Power 3', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Phonemax Rocky 2', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Zen Cinemax Prime', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Smart 2', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 9', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP GL255', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Studio G4', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 10 GT', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/1.8 + 24 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Fun 18×9', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'HomTom H10', 'manufacturer': 'Homtom', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos X9', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Fly Life Mega', 'manufacturer': 'FLY', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Spice F311', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Staari 12', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry EvolveX', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Prime 18×9 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP G250', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji Z9', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.42 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5512L Strike Forward', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5702 Spring', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 6.1 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture, 1.0 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry Evolve', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Spice K601', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Prime 18×9 3G', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody X24', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei P smart+ (Plus)', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 2 Megapixels with Digital zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5515L Fast', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio X1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oeina R8S Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S70', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C9', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vernee T3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Vernee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Spice F305', 'manufacturer': 'Spice', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5077', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei nova 3i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP + 2 Megapixels with Digital zoom'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24 Megapixels + 2 Megapixel with F2.0 Aperture, CMOS BSI Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with Emotion 8.2 UI'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 3 Mini', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Lava Z61', 'manufacturer': 'Lava', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '6 Megapixels LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gionee F205', 'manufacturer': 'Gionee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5076', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Max 3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar X1 Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y71i', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Wiko Sunny 3', 'manufacturer': 'Wiko', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Twin', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi i2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu 16', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C9A', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5075', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Infinix Note 5', 'manufacturer': 'Infinix', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kyocera Kantan Sumaho', 'manufacturer': 'Kyocera', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Prestigio Muze G7 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Prestigio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos C7A', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody D23', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1S Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Karbonn Aura Champ', 'manufacturer': 'Karbonn', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'TP-LINK Neffos P1', 'manufacturer': 'TP-LINK', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Phoenix Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On8 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy On6', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.78 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xgody Y23', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Infie 33', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1S', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'PLUZZ PL4010 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Doov A55', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Texet TM-5081', 'manufacturer': 'Texet', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV9500', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 V 2nd Gen', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 V 3th Gen', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Infie 3', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Supra Smartphone Full Specification', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 MP with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash, 1.12 um Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'PLUZZ PL5510 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola One Power', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'MyPhone Hammer Energy 18×9', 'manufacturer': 'MyPhone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno F2 LTE', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Game', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yes'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee F2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel U3 2018', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Jean', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP552', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Jinga Joy Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Jinga', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Irbis SP517', 'manufacturer': 'Irbis', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao S6 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Wieppo E1', 'manufacturer': 'Wieppo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V96', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P612', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Gome C71', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 2.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview A20 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels + 0.3 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with F2.8 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO GOLF2', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ZenFone Ares', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '22 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 aperture, 85 degree wide angle lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gome S1', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 1.5 (Android 6.1 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Motorola Moto E5 Cruise', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP with F2.2 Aperture, LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Zoji S12', 'manufacturer': 'Zoji', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P521', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone S9 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Rear camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, f/2.4 Aperture, Face Recognition, Interpolated resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Asus ROG Phone', 'manufacturer': 'ASUS', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 84 Degree Wide Angle Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo with ROG Gaming X Mode UI'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 SE', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '20 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with MIUI V9'}
{'device_name': 'Energizer Hardcase H500S', 'manufacturer': 'Energizer', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO GOLF1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Pear', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic Toughbook FZ-T1', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BLU C6', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Kenxinda W50', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee F2', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 8.0 (Android 7.1.1 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO HOT1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Selfie Camera'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GF7', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Poptel P9000 Max', 'manufacturer': 'Poptel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo Z5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 MP + 8 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO Mini1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'None'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 5.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-6015L Universe', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pop 1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 7.0 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Camon i Click', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylusα', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO G1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V92', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Micromax Canvas 2 Plus (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Micromax', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 3.3 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 3.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J7 Refine', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/1.7'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels f/1.9 with Samsung ISOCELL Sensor'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL4015', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5-Megapixel Main Auto Focus With Flash'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P2170', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3 Megapixel Dual Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Yes'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3 128GB', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Nokia 2.1', 'manufacturer': 'Nokia', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Achieve', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo K5 Note (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL4010', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pouvoir 2 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS 2.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit W289', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.29 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A8 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16MP+24MP with LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24MP Front Camera with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 6 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi Y2', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V9.5 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-4077 Shark Mini', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'QMobile Blue 5', 'manufacturer': 'QMobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO G4', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + O.3 MP with Dual-LED Flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy Amp Prime 3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel G9', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition, Interpolated Resolution 8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Digma Linx Trix 4G', 'manufacturer': 'Digma', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Oukitel OK6000 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Oukitel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Spark 2 Go Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Gome U7 mini', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS 2.0 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel S11', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J3 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels f/1.9'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels f/2.2 with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos Sense Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Fire', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '23.79 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gome S7', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'GEECOO G3', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Wolf', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi Pad 4', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP, f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android x.0 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gooweel S9', 'manufacturer': 'Gooweel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP+0.3MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels with LED Flash, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 5.1 Lollipop'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy A9 Star', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'BlackBerry KEY2', 'manufacturer': 'Blackberry', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 12 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/2.2 Aperture, 1.120 µm Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Panasonic P90', 'manufacturer': 'Panasonic', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with LED Flash, F2.2 Aperture, 4P Lens'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo NEX S', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gome Fenmmy Note', 'manufacturer': 'Gome', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Gome OS (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '24.77 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.1 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Allview A9 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo NEX', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5111L Bliss', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 6', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition,1.120 µm Pixel Size'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo Find X', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '20.11 MP f/2.0 + 16 MP f/2.0'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '25 MP, f/2.0'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M6T', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5707 Next', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress New', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Frost', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'VKworld K1', 'manufacturer': 'VKworld', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '21.46 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Phonic', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo R5', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Intex Aqua Lions T1 Lite VR', 'manufacturer': 'Intex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Click', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Stylo 4', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'OKWU Pi Plus', 'manufacturer': 'OKWU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0.1 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaolajiao 7P', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaolajiao', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Freeme OS 7.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion B145', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 7C Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Disco', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4160 x 3120 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S6 Selfie', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Guophone V19', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi V5', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S6 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V150', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'BLU Grand M3', 'manufacturer': 'BLU', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S509', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'dido 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo GM3', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Cherry Mobile Flare S6', 'manufacturer': 'Cherry Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '13.38 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Aristo 2 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q Stylus Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Guophone V88', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee S12', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Dido OS 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Avvio A50', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'InnJoo Smartron', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Koobee F1', 'manufacturer': 'Koobee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Dido OS 7.6 (Android 6.0 Marshmallow)'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Spring', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1600 x 1200 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Play', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel f/2.2 + 2 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition, 1080P'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo (EMUI 8.2) OS'}
{'device_name': 'Guophone XP9800', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'InnJoo Halo3 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee S55', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '2.07 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'InnJoo Spark', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'iVooMi i2', 'manufacturer': 'iVoomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'EL W45', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp X4', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Alcatel 3L', 'manufacturer': 'Alcatel', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P515', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor 9i', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 2 Megapixels with 2.0um Pixel Size, F2.0 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C1 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'InnJoo Netsurfer', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Wide 3', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Lenovo A5', 'manufacturer': 'Lenovo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Redmi 6A', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 MP'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 (Oreo), planned upgrade to Android 9.0 (Pie) + MIUI 9.0'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8 Explorer Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '19.66 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MIUI V10 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P520', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.3-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'InnJoo Voto', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Walton Primo RX6', 'manufacturer': 'Walton', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Z1', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch 4.0 OS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit C155', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Doogee X50L', 'manufacturer': 'Doogee', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Sony Xperia XZ3', 'manufacturer': 'Sony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '19.2 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony i75', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V140', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Enjoy 8e Youth', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS370 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 8MP f/2.0 with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.4 Front Camera with LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5510', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5-Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Allview Soul X5 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Allview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Visual UI (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Meizu M8C', 'manufacturer': 'Meizu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'FlyMe 7.0 (Android 7.1.2 Nougat)'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V44', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz PL5010', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS370', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13MP + 8MP f/2.0 with Dual-LED flash and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixel f/2.4 Front Camera with LED flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat OS'}
{'device_name': 'InnJoo Maze', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP Ixion B140', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '0.31 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo A73s', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Color OS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS180', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels with Single-LED and AF Rear Camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixel Front Camera with LED Flash'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Bear', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Sharp Aquos S3 High Edition', 'manufacturer': 'Sharp', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12 Megapixels + 13 Megapixels (Dual Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels with f/2.0 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Smile UX (Android 8.0 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Vivo Y81', 'manufacturer': 'Vivo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels with F2.2 Aperture, Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Funtouch OS 4.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'CMCC A3S', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'EL W40', 'manufacturer': 'EL', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5MP'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 6.0 Marshmallow'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS185', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Gigaset GS180', 'manufacturer': 'Gigaset', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart N9', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'Vodafone Smart N9 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Unknown', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'N/A'}, 'operating_system': 'N/A'}
{'device_name': 'ZTE Blade V8Q', 'manufacturer': 'ZTE', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Oppo F7 Youth', 'manufacturer': 'OPPO', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'ColorOS 5.0 (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Xiaomi Mi 8', 'manufacturer': 'Xiaomi', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels + 16 Megapixels (Dual Rear Camera)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with Face Recognition'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo with MIUI V9'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5206L Balance', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio X1 Note', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q7', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q7 Plus', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio S1 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C2 Lite', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Q7 Alpha', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C2', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Moto Qingyou XT1799', 'manufacturer': 'Motorola', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixel'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Comio S1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy S Light Luxury', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '16 Megapixels f/1.7, 1.12µm'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with f/1.7 Aperture, 1.22µm & Auto focus'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo OS'}
{'device_name': 'Comio P1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13.13 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J8', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Comio C1', 'manufacturer': 'Comio', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2560 x 1920 pixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Tecno Pouvoir 2', 'manufacturer': 'Tecno', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'HiOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'LG X5 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '3.15 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Cubot J3 Pro', 'manufacturer': 'Cubot', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo Go Edition'}
{'device_name': 'LG X2 (2018)', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Blackview BV5800', 'manufacturer': 'Blackview', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar XQ Dual', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'LG Premier Pro LTE', 'manufacturer': 'LG', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1 NOugat'}
{'device_name': 'Mobiistar CQ', 'manufacturer': 'Mobiistar', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.1.2 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit A250', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8.36 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'BQ Mobile BQ-5001L Contact', 'manufacturer': 'BQ Mobile', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Senseit N151', 'manufacturer': 'Senseit', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '2.09 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Vertex Impress Play', 'manufacturer': 'Vertex', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '15.93 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Huawei Honor Play 7', 'manufacturer': 'Huawei', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Ulefone X', 'manufacturer': 'Ulefone', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '13 Megapixels + 5 Megapixels Dual Back camera'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels with F2.4 Aperture, LED Flash, Face Recognition, Interpolated resolution 13 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'DEXP BS150', 'manufacturer': 'DEXP', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '1.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P513', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Symphony V120', 'manufacturer': 'Symphony', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '5.04 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 7.0 Nougat'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P5130', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '1.3-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Geecoo Selfie 1', 'manufacturer': 'Geecoo', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '8 Megapixels + 8 Megapixels'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.1 Oreo'}
{'device_name': 'Pluzz P212', 'manufacturer': 'Pluzz', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '0.08-Megapixel'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': 'Not Available'}, 'operating_system': 'No'}
{'device_name': 'Doov C70', 'manufacturer': 'Doov', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '4.92 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Yun OS 5.1.1 (Android)'}
{'device_name': 'Meitu T9', 'manufacturer': 'Meitu', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '12.19 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'MEIOS (Android 8.1 Oreo)'}
{'device_name': 'Samsung Galaxy J6', 'manufacturer': 'Samsung', 'rear_camera': {'resolution': '12.98 MP (megapixels)'}, 'front_camera': {'resolution': '7.99 MP (megapixels)'}, 'operating_system': 'Android 8.0 Oreo'}
